

# GENÍS GILAVERT BERLANA

Diluvi nº 7, 2º 2ª, Barcelona 08012

**4** 93 448 36 23 **609 156 909** 

■ anonymousheimer@gmail.com

https://github.com/anonymousHeimerdinger

#### **SUMMARY**

Leadership skills, analytic capacity and excellent problem solving skills.

Big potential in mathematics and programming.

Two years in the mathematics degree with mention in computing.

At change of job to computer systems administrator, stopped the carreer and continued expanding knowledge with others programming languages.

Currently, working and studying several courses of Programming and English in order to improve and look for job level challenges.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

Waiter January 1997 to January 1999

Bar Oasis - Hospitalet de Llobregat

Football referee January 1998 to January 2004
Federació Catalana de Futbol - Barcelona

**Bellboy** March 2002 to June 2002

Grupo de Hoteles Gargallo - Barcelona

Collaborator October 2004 to October 2004

Jornadas Internacionales de fisioterapia - Barcelona

**Commercial** November 2004 to January 2005 **Publingenios -** Barcelona

Administrative Assistant
Air France - Tremblay-en-France

January 2005 to September 2005

Network Operator for telefonica October 2005 to December 2005 Spark Ibérica - Barcelona

Soldier in the specialty of transmissions

April 2006 to August 2017

Ministerio de Defensa - Madrid

**Teacher of programing of Video Games with POO and Javascript** March, 22th 2019 **Espai Barcelona** - I was invited to give a class of programing

Computer systems administrator
Omega Peripherals - Barcelona
May 2017 to August 2019

**Developer** September 2019 to Currently Altran - Barcelona

#### **TRAINING**

Federació Catalana de Futbol Camp	1998
Barcelona	
Football referee title: Sports	
Institut Eduard Fontserè	2003

Hospitalet de Llobregat

Baccalaureate title: Technological

Dirección General de Tráfico

Barcelona

2003

Driving license class B
Spark Ibérica 2005

Barcelona
Network Operator course: Computing

Acuartelamiento San Fernando	2011
Zaragoza IT Essentials course: PC Hardware and Softwa	re: Computing
CAMPUS 25	2011
Barcelona University access certificate	
Universitat Pompeu Fabra	2013
Barcelona <b>Decoding Algebra course: Mathematics</b>	
Universitat Autónoma de Barcelona	2017
Barcelona  Course 1 of Design and creation of videogames	: Videogames programing
Universitat de Barcelona	2017
Barcelona Two years in the mathematics degree with men	ntion in computing: Pure
mathematics	
subjects of computing degree:	
Algorísmica	
<ul><li>Programació II</li><li>Estructura de dades</li></ul>	
<ul><li>Disseny de Software</li><li>Projecte Integrat de Software</li></ul>	
Commvault	2018
New Jersey Commvault Technical Sales Professional - CVT	SP10
Espai	2018
Barcelona Higher course of development and implement	ation of web applications
I designer	not finished yet
Barcelona Programing of Video Games with Unreal Engin	ω'
CEPI-BASE	2019
Barcelona Course of Visual C#/C++.NET	
CEPI-BASE	not finished yet
Barcelona SQL	
ELMUNDODELBECARIO.COM	2019
Barcelona <b>XML</b>	
CALLAN SCHOOL OF ENGLISH	not finished yet
Barcelona Stage 6 and 7 of the Callan method	
KNOWLEDGES, SKILLS AND APTITUDES	
<u>Programming languages</u> <u>A</u>	<u>pplications</u>

#### <u>Programming languages</u>

C, C++, C#, R, Java, Mathematica, Powershell, Python, PHP, JSP and Javascript

# Others languages

XML, HTML5, CSS3, jquery, Linux, JSON, ajax and SQL  $\,$ 

### **Languages**

Native: Spanish, Catalan Medium: English (level B1, studying for B2 offical exam)

#### <u>Applications</u>

Videogame: Bubbles math competition of web videogames

backup analysis free

Videogame: FlyAway Android subject "integrated software project"

Multimedia player subject "programing II"

Java

# Programming projects

**Test web** PHP php final exam

**Commercial web** HTML5 and CSS3

#### **Code Editors**

Netbeans, AndroidStudio, Mathematica, Eclipse, Microsoft Visual Studio and Visual Studio Code

# **Work platforms**

Git, ElasticSearch, OpenCMS, Unreal Engine 4, OpenGL and unity 3D

# **Ticketing tools**

CRM, ServiceNow and JIRA mainly ...

html final exam

Kangaroo service subject "software design'

movies and series service

subject "software design'

Other programs C and C++

Java

Java

#### various subjects

#### AWARDS AND ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS

# university awards

Oualification of Honor's Registration in the subject "Elements de programació"

#### other awards

Contest of programming a math videogame in Javascript

# individual sports

#### **❖** Athletics

- 1º Classified T cross of "Hospitalet de Llobregat"
- 1º Classified Trophy "ROBERTO CABREJAS" in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE" (3 km) Obtaining the record of the lower time in the institute`s history
- 10 Classified T Militar trophy "Trofeo SAN FERNANDO" (5 km) in the army

Between the position 100 and 200 of 60 thousand participants in the race of "El Corte inglés" (about 12,5 km in 41 minutes)

#### ir Chess

- 10 Classified T tournament in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"
- 1º Classified T League in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"
- 1º Classified T summer tournament in a English school camp

# Shot with long weapon

10 Classified T Militar trophy "SAN FERNANDO" in the army

# **☞** Videogames

1º Classified **?** 2 times at tournament of "Super Smash Bros"

# collective sports

# Football

- 1º Classified T Many trophies of league "LAS PLANAS"
- 1º Classified T Champions league "LAS PLANAS"
- 1º Classified T summer tournament played in zone Pedralbes in barcelona

# **Volleyball**

10 Classified T tournament in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"

# **☞** Videogames

Diamond level playing "League of Legends"

In the 10 best players of the world with the champion Heimerdinger in "League of Legends" 10 Classified T tournament of couples playing at "Pro Evolution Soccer"